RG 169:007, Connecticut Forest and Park Association
Connecticut State Library
- Series 12. Photographs, 1900-2011
  - Publication Materials, 1913-2001
    - Photographs-possibly used in brochures, 1940-1960 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Printer positives for publishing, undated (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Signs, table cards and name tags, undated (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Woodlands, photographs from Connecticut Woodlands, 1995 Summer-1999; Photographs and photocopies; photocopy of coyote slide by Paul Rego, slide in box 41 folder 5 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - CFPA, 100 years of conservation 1895 - 1995, undated; 8 1/2" CFPA logo mounted on board (Box 48)
    - Project learning tree, undated; 12" logo is printed on material (Box 48)
  - Portraits, 1929-2007
    - Anagnostakis, Sandra L., Connecticut Agricuture Experiment Station, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Arthur, George, roving trails crew, Connecticut Forest and Park Association Volunteer Trail Manager, 1999 September (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Bailey, Kornel at his home in Haddam, 1992 April (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Barton, Hedy, Director of Development during capitol fund drive, circa 1980 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Blake, Dick, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Brenneman, Russell L., 1980-1999 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Camp, John R. (Jack), 1989; Some photographs include John Ellsworth. (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Casey, Dan, Volunteer of the Year, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Colson, Ann, Trails Coordinator and Director of Volunteers, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Foresters, 1976-1996 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Formey, J.W., undated (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Gluck, Emery at Cockaponsett State Forest, 1999 Fall (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Heermance, Edgar Laing, Secretary of Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1935 January (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - Hibbard, John and Bernice, Linda, 1970-2000; Also an early photograph of Hibbard at a display booth, location unknown. (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - Keeney, Timothy R.E., Department of Environmental Protection Commissioner, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - LaBella, Elaine, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - Libby, George, 1980-1990 (Box 40, Folder 36)
    - Milne, George, 1980-2007 (Box 40, Folder 37)
    - Morrison, Bob, Trails Protection Subcommitte, 1999 September (Box 40, Folder 38)
    - Murphy, Maureen, circa 1990 (Box 40, Folder 39)
    - Nash, Dan, 1992-1999 (Box 40, Folder 40)
    - O'Neill, William A., Governor, 1986 June 10 (Box 40, Folder 41)
    - Pendergast, Patricia, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 42)
    - Picone, Peter, Wildlife Biologist, Department of Environmental Protection, undated (Box 40, Folder 43)
    - Rankin, Kathy, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 44)
    - Richardson, Ed and Marion, 2000 June 6 (Box 40, Folder 45)
    - Ross, Robert M., 1929 December 26 (Box 40, Folder 46)
    - Sills, Norm, 1999 November; Some photographs include Dick Whitehouse. (Box 40, Folder 47)
    - Connecticut Forest and Park Association staff and directors, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 48)
    - Taberman, Ray, Trails Manager, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 49)
    - Therrien, Linda, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 50)
    - Whitehouse, Dick, 1999 November; Some photographs also include Norm Sills and Russ Brenneman. (Box 40, Folder 51)
    - Wheatley, Jim, volunteer, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 52)
    - Zimmer, Norm, Vice Chair, Meriden Conservation Commission, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - Photograph Albums, 1921-2007
    - Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 100th Anniversary Gala, 1995 (Box 43, Folder Item 1)
    - The Connecticut Forest and Park Association; final campaign report, undated; Notes and photographs of groundbreaking and building of headquarters. (Box 43, Folder Item 2)
    - Tree Farms, Connecticut Forest and Park Association meetings and 25th anniversary, 1921 July-1991; Album contains photographs on the following subjects: Experiment Station, Jones Tree Farm, Camp Tree Farm, Hammonasset, Sunny Valley Farm, Bushnell Park, Connecticut Forest and Park Association field meetings and outings, trails meetings, Hurricane Gloria damage, and Metropolitian District Commission West Hartford reservoir. (Box 43, Folder Item 3)
    - Photo Album, large variety of places, 1964-2007; Album contains photographs on the following subjects: Beaver Brook, Black Rock, Bolton Notch, Burr Pond, Chatfield Hollow, Dennis Hill, Devils, Hopyard, Chapman Falls, Cockapauset, Gay City, Fort Shantok, Fort Griswold, Flanders Nature Center, Indian Museum, Goodwin Forest, Gillette Castle, Hopeville Pond, Haystack Mountain, Hurd Park, Haddam Island, Hog Back Dam, Indian Well, Kettletown, Saint Johns Ledges, Miller's Pond, Mashomoquet, Lake Warramug, Appalachian Mountain Club (AMC) trails, Lake Waramaug, Mount Riga, Mansfield Hollow, Osbornedale Park, Mohawk Forest, Meshamosic Forest, Nipmuck Forest, Pachaug Forest, Peoples Forest, Platt Hill, Penwood Park, Natchaug Forest, Nathan Hale Forest, Ross Pond, Rocky Neck, Selden Neck, Sherwood Island, Squantz Pond, Salmon River Forest, Stoddard Hill, Stratton Brook, Shenipsit Forest, Sharon Audubon, Tunxis Forest, Talcott Mountain, Wadsworth Falls, Wolf Den, and Castle Craig. (Box 43, Folder Item 4)
    - Photographs, undated; Album contains photgraphs possibly taken at headquarters. (Box 43, Folder Item 5)
    - Association Field Meeting, Jones Tree Farm, 1963-1972; Album contains photographs on the following subjects: 4-H Project, Cranska Oaks, Matthies Plaque, Peoples State Forest, Destruction of Shade Trees, White Memorial foundation, Pinchot Sycamore, Sleeping Giant State Park, Goodwin State Forest and Conservation Center, Great Pond Forest, Natchaug Forest, Shepard Memorial - Nye Holman Forest, Old State House, Great Trail, Pachaug State Forest, Flanders Nature Center, Silver Fir Tree planting commemorative Silver Anniverary, Christmas Tree exhibit and Growers Association, Governor's Conference on Natural and Enviornmental Beauty with letter by Hibbard, Elm Mortaltiy, American Youth Hostel meeting, Austin Hawes Campground, Talcott Mountain State Forest, Great Pond State Forest, Enders State Forest and dog cemetery, Hemlock Reservoir, Route 2 highway, Blackledge River, and Connecticut - Rhode Island Trust Farm Committee. (Box 44, Folder Item 1)
  - Posters, 1970-2010
    - Join us in celebrating - Year of the forest, 1990; Folder includes poster, mockup and 4"x5" color negative of trees used for the poster. (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Commemorating Seventy-five years of the Blue-Blazed hiking trails, 2004; Illustration by Bill Thomson (Box 49, Folder Item 1)
    - Forces of nature, 2007 November 9; A Play commissioned by CFPA and presented as a staged dramatic reading in Hartford, CT; there are five hand signed signatures on the poster (Box 49, Folder Item 2)
    - Connecticut trails day celebration, 2010 June 5 (Box 49, Folder Item 3)
- Series 13. Slides, 1907-2002
  - State Parks and Forests, 1940-2000 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Transplanting in nursery, 1940 April 30; Slide possibly Pleasant Valley.
    - Charcoal Kiln, Meshomasick, 1940 April 30
    - Getting out pulp wood, circa 1940; "On road - 2 cords per day per [text illegible] 1.75 to haul 26 miles", possibly Shepard wood utilization work.
    - Mount Carmel, Sleeping Giant, 1940 October 16
    - Hurricane thrown Spruce, circa 1940; 1938 hurricane damage.
    - Wood piled on Barnes Road - Peoples, 1940; Possibly made by Civilian Conservation Corps (CCC).
    - South [text illegible] Legion, circa 1941
    - Mount Tom Pond, 1941 April 10
    - Salmond River Bridge, circa 1942; Rebuilt by Civilian Conservation Corps (CCC).
    - Laurel at Natchaug, circa 1942
    - Sherwood Island Park, circa 1942
    - Hurd Park, 1945 October 10
    - Hurd Park, River Swell, 1945 October 10
    - Hurd Park, old barn - fireplaces, 1945 October 10
    - Hurd Park, boat landing, 1945 October 10
    - Spruce Swamp, Mohawk, circa 1945; Possibly photographed by Bill Shepard and Archie Hurford.
    - Sumac in fall, circa 1945
    - Gilette Castle, circa 1945; 3 slides
    - Conifer Nursery, Pachug, circa 1945
    - Pachug Nursery building when new, circa 1945
    - Pachug State Forest Nursery, circa 1945
    - Hammonasset Beach, Madison, 1947; Little girl on an outing, AWH 1947.
    - Probably State Forestry staff, circa 1950
    - Untitled, 1959; Dedication marker, group of people.; 2 slides
    - Forestry field discussion, 1960 August; 5 slides
    - Gardens at Harkness State Park, circa 1960; Slide marked JEH.
    - View of New Haven from East Rock Park, 1964 July; Slide marked JEH.
    - Sleeping Giant field meeting, 1964 October; Slide marked JEH.
    - Connecticut River Ramble scenes, 1964 October; Slide marked JEH.
    - Fire prevention demonstration, 1967 July; Slide marked JEH.
    - Great Pond State Forest, 1968 May; Slide marked JEH.
    - Entrance to headquarters, Shenipsit, 2000 March; Slides from Marilyn Aarestad.
    - J. L. Goodwin State Forest, Goodwin House, 2000 April 10; Slides from Marilyn Aarestad.
    - Nye-Holman State Forest, 2000 April 10; Slides from Marilyn Aarestad.
    - Natchaug, General Lyon, Civilian Conservation Corps (CCC) Camp Fernow, 2000 April 25; Slides from Marilyn Aarestad.
    - Salmon River State Forest recreation area, 2000 April 25; Slides from Marilyn Aarestad.
    - Falls Brook Trail, Tunxis State Forest, West Hartland, circa 2000
  - Trails, 1969-2002 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Satans Kingdom, Gorge - Tunxis Trail, 1969 October; Slide marked CSB, Slide dated Dec[ember] [19]87.
    - Sierra Club Hike, P. Brooks in Sages Ravine, 1969 June 8; Slide marked CSB, Slide dated Dec[ember] [19]87.
    - Gurley Mill, Nipmuck Trail, 1973 October 21; R. Brooks, Slide marked CSB, Slide dated Dec[ember] [19]87.
    - Cornwall Hollow, Appalachian Mountain Club (AMC) at hike, 1978 December 4; Slide marked EH/CSB, Slide dated Dec[ember] [19]87.
    - Shenipsit Trail, North Route 2, 1978 March 5; RBB, Ann and Emerson Harrison, Slide marked CSB, Slide dated Dec[ember] [19]87.
    - Shenipsit Trail, TNC hike, Birch Mountain section, 1979 October; Slide marked CSB, Slide dated Dec[ember] [19]87.
    - Hikers east of Sleeping Giant chin, 1983 April; Slide marked DMS.
    - Mattabesett - South, 1987 February; One slide marked W.wter.; 12 slides
    - Mattabesett - South Connecticut R., 1987 February; 3 slides
    - Mattabesett - Chauncey Peak, 1987 February; 4 slides
    - Mattabesett - Mount Higby, 1987 March; Cecilia.
    - Mattabesett - Mount Higby, 1987 March
    - Mattabesett - Mount Higby, 1987 March; Elaine.
    - Mattabesett - Higby section, 1987 March
    - Mattabesett - Higby section, 1987 March; Anita, Allison, Cecilia.
    - Mattabesett - North, 1987 March; Cecilia.
    - Mattabesett - Mount section, 1987 March; Hiking group.
    - Mattabesett - Higby section, 1987 March; Linda Holenstein, her dog, Elaine.
    - Mattabesett - Mount Lamentah, 1987 March; Ruth.
    - Mattabesett - Mount Lamentah, 1987 March; Elaine, Barbara.
    - Mattabesett - Mount Lamentah, 1987 March
    - Mattabesett - Chauncey Peak, 1987 March; Ruth, Carol, Terry.
    - Mattatuck Trail, Wolcott, 1987 March; One slide identifies Buttermilk Falls.; 12 slides
    - Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1987 March; Headquarters and Connecticut Forest and Park Association sign.; 3 slides
    - Untitled, 1987 April; Headquarters, slide credits, maps and brochures.; 11 slides
    - Bushy Hill Nature Center, Ivoryton, 1987 April; 3 slides
    - Mohawk Trail, Coltsfoot Mountain, 1991 April 7; One slide marked as Bridge.; 12 slides
    - Nipmuck Marathon, 1993 June; 3 slides
    - Mohawk Trail, Coltsfoot Mountain, Furnace Brook Bridge, 1993 July; 14 slides
    - Brookfield Bridge, 1993 July; 4 slides
    - Falls Village, 1993 July; One slide marked Falls Village Beacon!; 6 slides
    - Lillinonah Trail, "Scenic Trail" sign, 1993 July
    - Untitled numbered group, 1993 August; Slides include the following subjects: Rocky Neck, Bluff Point, Penwood, Talcot Mountain, Harkness, and Connecticut and Forest Park Association headquarters.; 11 slides
    - Beckley Furnace, 2000 April; Photograph by Fred Warner, Walt Landgood.
    - Mount Pisgah, field property, Durham area, 2002 October; Adam's slides.; 20 slides
  - Programs, 1969-1999 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Trails Day, Mount Higby, 1993 May; Photograph by Linda Rapp.; 5 slides
    - Trails Day, Whitestone Cliffs Trail, Watertown, 1993 June; Possibily first annual, #108 Hicock.; 8 slides
    - Connecticut Envirothon Forestry, undated; Possibly duplicate slides.; 15 slides
    - Earth Day Project, Cheney Technical; Barnes Nature Center workshop; Case Mountain: water bar, Shenipsit reroute; and Trails Day hike, 1993 April 23-June 5; 15 slides (Folder 1-2)
    - Durham first graders, Highlawn TF, 1993 May; Photographs by Youell.; 5 slides
    - Releaf, 1994 November; School children wear tee shirts marked: Park City Center Urban Forestry Crew. Photographs removed to Programs/Releaf/Bpt. One slide marked 1992 Lang Photo.; 5 slides
    - Ann's hiking slide show, 1982-1999; Text available, slides removed from carousel.; 102 slides
    - Bluff Point, Groton, 1969-1987; Slides by Sydney Van Zandt. Slides removed from carousel.; 112 slides (Folder 2-3)
    - Keeping Connecticut Green, Together today ... for tomorrow, 1972-1992; Slides consist of the following subjects: 6 Rules for Prevention of Fires in Connecticut, line drawings of headquarters, farms, waterfalls, and Heubline Tower-Talcott Mountain. Many are copy slides. See sound recording series for sound cassette.; 68 slides + supplemental material
    - Land Trust, 1994 November 5; 80 slides
    - Youell's adapted 100 year slide show, 1996 January; Text available, slides are marked as duplicates.; 41 slides (Folder 3-4)
  - Workshops, 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Maintainer's workshop, 1993 April; 23 slides
    - Maintainer's workshop, 1993 April-May; 14 slides
    - Work party, making the Connecticut River extension, Mattabesett Trail, 1993 Spring; 4 slides
    - Trail maintenance workshop, Tunxis Trail, 1993 October 26; 5 slides
    - Maintainer's workshop, 1994 July; Slides consist of the following subjectes: blazing, bridge, dredging, John Rek moving logs, and side hiking.; 8 slides
    - Work parties, 1994 Spring; Slides consist of the following subjects: Brookfield bridge dedication, Pomeraug, Paugussett, Mohawk trail, Cathederal Pines, and Deans Ravine Brook. Slides from Richard Blake. Slides marked 1993-1994; 26 slides
    - Bridge work, Case Mountain, 1994 Spring; Slides from Whitehouse.; 11 slides
  - Events, 1960-2000 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Connecticut Forest and Park Association meeting at Great Pond, undated
    - Field meeting, Xmas tree planting, 1960 August; 2 slides
    - Trails dinner, 1992; Slide dated May 1993.; 3 slides
    - Trails for Tomorrow Award, 1993 August; Includes a slide of Yosemite Lembert Dome and Reno.; 5 slides
    - Untitled, 1993 November; A large group of people possibly for a dinner at headquarters.
    - Untitled, 1994 June; Slides 0-18 shows a city park with children and posters; and slides 20-24 are of hiking and possibly a quarry.; 24 slides
    - Connecticut Forest and Park Association annual meeting and dedication of Camp Demonstration Forest and open house, 2000 May 6-June 6; Group tour. Photographs have been removed to photograph series.; 14 slides
  - Buildings, 1962-2000 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Connecticut Arboretum Lodge, 1962 May
    - State Capitol, office at 1010 Main Street, East Hartford, 1983 April; Jay Furlazo and John Hibbard.; 10 slides
    - Connecticut Forest and Park Association headquarters sign and library, 1996 November; 2 slides
    - Connecticut Forest and Park Association headquarters, 2000 Fall; 4 slides
  - Landscapes, 1940-1996 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Tree varieties, 1940 June 18-1947 November; Includes a slide of Housatonic Forest, Mount Tom State Park, and Native Rhododendron.; 18 slides
    - Shade trees and street scenes, Urban Forestry of 1950's, 1950-1957; Includes a beaver house, Lady Sycamore tree and Shepard's Cordwood contraption in Pachaug.; 17 slides
    - Trees, circa 1950; Unidentified - trees along the roadside.; 14 slides
    - Dutch Elm disease, circa 1950; Yellow flag, Whalley Avenue, and Westville.; 2 slides (Folder 5)
    - Trees and leaves, circa 1950; Identified trees and close up of leaves.; 6 slides
    - Untitled, 1959 July; One slide has 4 unidentified personnel.; 3 slides
    - Trees, Christmas trees and Connecticut Forest and Park Association field meeting, 1960 October; 9 slides
    - Wood cutting, stumps, and snow scene Blue Blaze trail, 1973 May-1976 April; 4 slides
    - Dirt clearing, 1984 May
    - Flowers, 1982 May-1987 April; Variety of plants and flowering bushes. Slides by Jay, Matt Donachie and others.; 39 slides
    - Tree cutting, 1991 April; Person cutting pine tree.
    - Lamentah closed, 1993 April; 6 slides
    - Black Pond Park, a Meriden City Park, 1994 March; Slide by D.M. Smith.
    - Hemlocks and Mark McClure, 1994 June
    - Fire, 1996 May
  - Exhibit Materials, 1970-1999 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Keep Connecticut Green, circa 1970; Tri-fold poster display.
    - Dutch Elm disease control, circa 1970; Tri-fold poster display, posssibly Greenwich Tree Department.
    - The National Wildlife Federation, 1988; Scenic view.
    - National Trails Day banner, 1993 June 5
    - Geological map of Connecticut, 1994 August; Landscapes of Connecticut.
    - Zoological Society of San Diego, 1999; Commercial duplicates.; 6 slides
  - Publication Materials, 1973-1992 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Sitting at desk, 1973 August; Possibly at headquarters. Photograph removed to publication folder.
    - Coyote photos, 1992 May; Used for Coyote article, 1999. Slides by Paul Rego; photocopy in box 40 folder 19.; 2 slides
    - Farmland article, 1973 August; CW-9 cover shot and CW-10 inside front cover. Photographs removed to publication materials, farmland article. l slide by Barbara Sherman.; 2 slides
    - Connecticut Forest and Park Association title page and office-line drawings, undated; 3 slides
  - Collections, 1907-1990 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Shade trees, Dutch Elm and other topics, 1940-1960; Slides consist of the following topics: Pachaug Nursery, Civilian Conservation Corps (CCC) people; Dutch Elm disease; tree specimens; California and Mexico; and Northern New England wild flowers. Also includes: Bluff Point, Mystic River, Billboard signs, Natchaug Forest, Trailer Camp at Peoples Forest, Mount Tom, Kent Falls, Farmington River, Moosehead Lake, and Downer State Forest in Vermont.; 120 slides
    - South West Connecticut Scenery, Greenfield Hill Dogwoods and Silvermine area, 1944-1950; Topics include: silvermine, dogwoods, Bradley's old axe factory in Lyon's Plain, Lovers Leap, Putnam Pond in Redding, Roton Point in South Norwalk. Slides by C.A. Owens Senior.; 71 slides (Folder 6)
    - Haley Farm, Bluff Point, 1970-1978 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Haley Farm, Bluff Point, 1970-1978; Flora; Point Lobos; wild flowers; Mystic River; from Claiborne C. Van Zandt, Jr.; 164 slides (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Slides stamped: SNET CO.; from glass slides and State Parks, 1907-1990; 1907-1920's; 1930's includes Civilian Conservation Corps (CCC) Camps; and 1960-1980's includes State Parks, Connecticut Forest and Park Association office, maps and diagrams from glass slides, logo and publication covers.; 76 slides
  - Duplicate Groups of Slides, 1940-1986 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Xmass trees at Monroe, Connecticut, 1965; Probably Wagner Farm; slides by D.M. Smith.
    - Bus trip, 1979
    - Wilbur Cross Parkway, 1982 October; Taken from Ridge Road overpass in North Haven. Slides by D.M. Smith.
    - Elm trees: Enfield Town Hall and Cemetary, Saint Mary's Church in Hazardville, Thompsonville, Fuller School in Somers, Somerville, Mansfield, and other unidentified locations, circa 1940; 2 slides are encased in glass.; 22 slides
    - Trails through towns, 1972-1986; Towns covered in slides include: Ashford, Barkhamsted, Burlington, Guilford, Hamden, Hebron, Kent, Mansfield, Meriden, Middlefield, Middletown, Plymouth, North Pauguset, Simsbury, Southington, Tarrifville, Thomaston, Unionville, Voluntown, Watertown, and Wolcott. Slides by Matt Donachie.; 46 slides (Folder 7-8)
    - Trails by name, undated; Trails covered in slides include: Housatonic, Mattabessett, Mattatuck, Metacomet, Natchaug, Nipmuck, Ragged Mountain, Shenipsit, Tunxis, and Vernon fungus.; 26 slides
    - Trails with hikers and views, undated; Trails covered in slides include: Agricultural Experiment Station in Hamden, Cockaponset, Macedonia, Mattabesett, Mattatuck, McLean Refuge, Metacomet, Mount Algo, Pachaug, and Shenipsit.; 25 slides
    - Trails, undated; Blue Blazed Trails. Slides by Cara Lee.; 17 slides
    - Appalachian trail, State Park vistas, State Forest, and incomplete numbered set 1-138, undated; Locations in slides include: Blue Trails bronze plaque, Bulls Bridge, Cornwall, Falls Village, Hamden, Hawk Watch, Barn Door Hill-McLean Refuge, Horse Trail, Kent, Macedonia, Mattatuck, Monroe, Paugussett, Peoples Forest, Sherman, and tightwire crossing. People identified in slides: Ned Anderson, John Dowd, and Norm Sills.; 30 slides
    - Hiking groups and repeated duplicates, undated; Slides consist of the following topics: American Legion-Peoples State Forest-Coal mound, Macedonia summit of Cobble Mountain in Kent, and winter scenes.; 61 slides
    - Vistas, trails, snow scenes and repeated duplicates, undated; Slides consist of the following topics: Avon Mountain tower, East Granby Land Trust signage, flowers, maps and brochures, Mattabesset in Middletwon and Middlefield Black Pond, Nipmuck, Western Mattatuck Trail, Paugussett trail in Monroe or Shelton, and Sleeping Giant.; Possibly used for "Hiking Connecticut's blue-blazed trails" slide show with text and sound. See sound recording series for sound cassette.; 41 slides
- Series 14. Scrapbooks, circa 1921-1994
  - Scrapbooks, 1924-1945; 2 volumes (Box 27)
  - Scrapbooks, 1985-1994; 2 volumes (Box 27)
  - Scrapbooks, circa 1921-1950; 2 volumes (Box 28)
    Scrapbook, circa 1921-1939, contains a few black-and-white photographs and prints of the Flood of 1936 and Hurricane of 1938.
  - Scrapbooks, 1950-1957; 2 volumes (Box 29)
  - Haley Farm scrapbook, 1963-1966, undated; 1 volume (Box 30)
    Scrapbook contains newspaper clippings, souvenir pamphlet, programs, and photographs covering the topics of Haley Farm and the Connecticut River Ramble.
  - Scrapbooks, 1957-1966; 2 volumes (Box 30)
- Series 15. Maps, 1929-1978
  - Avon, Connecticut, 1957; Quadrangle Topographic and Highway map. (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Connecticut mini maps, 1929-1935; State parks picture plan, distribution of Capitol Outlay and use. (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Forest and hiking map booklets, 1929-1964; Cockaponset State Forest, July 1930; Hiking Connecticut's Blue-Blazed Trails, undated; Hiking Trails of New England, 1964; Mohawk State Forest, May 1929; and Peoples and American Legion State Forests, July 1929.; 5 folded booklets (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Glacial Geology of Connecticut, circa 1930; Large topographic map. (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Isolines, circa 1949; Maps depict forested area, climate zones. waterlaid soil, annual snowfall, temperatures, soil groups, bedrock formations, and population. (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Connecticut local area trails, circa 1940-1970; Some maps also include correspondences and newspaper clippings: Bridgeport, Glastonbury, Manchester, Mattabesett, Mattatuck, Narragansett, Peoples and American Legion in Barkhamsted, Quinnipiac, Somers, Waterbury, and Winsted- Appalachian Mountain Club (A.M.C.) walk. (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Newark Group, 1949-1960; Newark formations, also includes a film negative of the map. (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Newington, Connecticut, circa 1931; Indian Hill Golf Club and area. (Box 45, Folder 8)